Narrator: 1
Speaker: This is for my foodie friends.
In case you thought lettuce was only for salads, here I’m cooking it in some butter with an onion.
Then I add some mushrooms, chicken, fresh tomatoes,
and some other things – not sure yet.
Lettuce is also great in soups, or you can grill it and serve it with blue cheese.
Narrator: 2
Speaker: We didn’t feel like cooking last night, and anyway we didn’t have
any food in the house, so we decided to order some takeaway
salads from our wonderful local pizzeria.
They were all very good, but my favourite was a chicken salad,
a bit like a Caesar salad, with carrots, tomatoes, peppers, lettuce,
and some pieces of fried bread.
Narrator: 3
Speaker: Dinner last night at a restaurant in Piccadilly, called NOPI.
We had lots of different sharing plates.
I loved everything, especially this dish called shakshuka, which is North African,
and it’s basically eggs in a tomato sauce, but the mixture of herbs and spices
makes it just fantastic.
And the bread we had to dip in the sauce was wonderful, too.
Go there. Soon.
Narrator: 4
Speaker: OK, this is it!
Our Thanksgiving dinner.
All the usual things, turkey with cranberry sauce, roast potatoes, mashed potatoes,
lots of vegetables, and more…and more…
We thought about going to a restaurant this year, maybe having seafood,
but then we decided, no, we like home-made and traditional,
so we stayed at home and cooked together.
So how was yours?